

Chaithanya Reddy

Full-Stack Web Developer

+91 9381374502

Punganur, Andhra Pradesh chaithanyareddy786@gmail.com

LinkedIn : Chaithanya Reddy

Github: chaitu786

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

An ambitious and self-motivated web developer with a considerable technical skill who possesses self- discipline and ability to work with minimum of supervision. Able to play a key role in website development to ensure maximum accessibility, user experience and usability. A quick learner who can absorb new ideas and can communicate clearly and effectively

PROJECTS

Inspired From Nykaa

A web application to buy Cosmetics products and Beauty products.

Features:

- Sign-in/Sign-up.
- Category-based products gallery.
- Sorting products.
- Adding and Removing products from cart.
- · Payment Page.
- User-friendly and interactive website.

Tech Stack: HTML | CSS | Javascript Areas of responsibility:

- Developed Signup and Login pages.
- Built product page as per the Categories.
- User-specific cart with adding and removing the products as well.
- Developed a payment page.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Site Coordinator/Hr Coordinator

Honda Motorcycle & Scooter India Pvt. Ltd, Karnataka

November 2020 - August 2021

- Interviewing the candidates and hiring the candidates as per the company requirements
- Joining process and Document Verification and ID card preparation
- Employees Trackers and Master Data Maintenance

In Plant Trainee

Keihin Fie Pvt. Ltd, Karnataka May 2019 - November 2019

- Updating the daily production details
- Updating daily rejecting components details
- Helping to subordinates during the production
- Monitor the Machines specifications

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Full-Stack Web Development

Masai School, Bangalore DECEMBER 2021 - Present

DIPLOMA IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

Dr. YC James Yen Govt. Polytechnic College, Kuppam

JULY 2017 - MARCH 2020

- Developed the sorting functionality for sorting the products by cost, discount,name etc.
- Developed a profile page for users.

A collaborative project built by a team of 6 executed in 6 days.

Inspired From Zoomcar (



A web application to provide self driven cars for rentals and car rentals.

Features:

- User authentication.
- Location-based vehicle gallery.
- Vehicle Booking page & Vehicle policies.
- Floating window navbar.
- · Payment page.
- Sorting.

Tech Stack: HTML | CSS | Javascript | Node.js

Areas of responsibility:

- Developed Signup and Login pages .
- Developed the Home using API.
- Developed the Location-based vehicle gallery.
- · Laid out the database schema and build the REST API for the same.
- Developed the sorting functionality for sorting the Vehicles by Seating Capacity ,vehicle type and Brand type etc.

A collaborative project built by a team of 5 executed in 6 days.

Class 10

Z P High School, Bandlapalle MONTH 2016 - MONTH 2017

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

HTML | CSS | MERN | AdvanceJS | React | Redux | MongoDB | TypeScript | DSA | Bootstrap

CERTIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

CISCO IT ESSENTIALS [2] MICROSOFT OFFICE ☑ SOLID EDGE [7] PYTHON BASICS ☐

SOFT SKILLS

Commitment Towards Work | Team Collaboration | Time Management |

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Volunteer Joining The Dots (JTD) December 2021 - Present

INTERESTS

Listening Music | Motivating | Cricket and Kabaddi